Let's get up at the Goodbar!
Yay!
Everybody team, everybody team
Let's split up
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
Oh, can we win?
I can win, I can win, I can win.
Oh.
My seriousness is catastrophically bad.
I am.
I'll start by explaining how to investigate Mike.
Then we'll have one person on each team
I'll do this one.
Here we go.
Ready?
Yes, sir.
Oh!
I can do this.
That wasn't so bad.
Mon-chan wins!
Rina-chan made me do it.
Rina-chan did it.
Please play safe!
So much for the step double eggs.
Sora and Rina-chan...
Sora and Rina have good seats.
If we can't separate them...
If we don't split up, it's as if we're all going to end up in the same place.
They split up nicely.
Mon-chan is over the train today.
Mon-chan is going over the train in the morning.
So we're all ready to go.
I already knew about this competition.
That's right.
I won.
Of course I won.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
If we lose, it'll be too much.
I'll do my best.
I'll cheer for you!
That's great!
Even the gas pedal's in front of you!
Like this!
It's like a scooter.
Electric?
It's like an electric scooter.
Wow!
Oh, my God.
This is so cute.
That's good, Solo.
That was so good!
Ya!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
It's good.
It's early.
I'm going.
Oh, I'm scared.
Again?
Which one was faster?
About the next one.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you for your hard work.
You're in O-chan's corner.
You are in O-chan's corner.
Ohkun is in Oh-chan's corner.
Ohkkun, you're playing for Daddy.
Ohkkun, Daddy's having fun.
Okkun, you're playing for Papa.
Oh, welcome back.
Ohkun, welcome back.
Welcome back, Daddy.
Thank you for your hard work.
Then, let's announce the results.
Okay, Yamai, what was your time?
I got 17 seconds.
Oh!
That's good.
10 seconds.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
That was so close.
That was fast.
Okay, I'm off.
Bye-bye.
Yes, please.
Okay.
Oh!
I knew it was the rim.
Well, then, these two are the watchdogs.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Come on, everybody.
Oh!
Ooh!
Ooh!OH!!!
Thank you for your hard work!
Everyone, eat your dinner!
Yay!
Ooh!
Oh!
Good job!
Everybody...
Whoa!
Oh!
Go, go, go, go!
How's it going?
Ooh!
Huh?
Why, why, why?
Come on!
Go, go, go!
Last one!
Ooh!
Ooh! Happy!
It's so good!
Delicious.
I don't have an appetite.
Put your butt in it.
Eh~
My first time.
Oh, no.
A little bit.
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh, but...
Ah~~
Ah!
Ahhh...
Ah~~
Aaaaahhh!
Ahhhhh...
I said it hurts
It hurts
I can do it. I can do it.
Oh, wait, I'm scared.
Come on.
Ow!
Ouch! Ouch!
Ow! Ow!
Ooh!
It's not broken.
Good job.
200 kilos.
206 kilos.
Happy 170 centimeters, Mr. *Oh*
Yes!
Good job, sir!
You did it again today.
Let's do it!
I thought Moe was the leader.
I'm Blue Doli. I'm actually good at sports.
I'm sorry.
I got a surprisingly high score at the family audition.
I was so surprised by Rina's athletic ability.
I was so surprised.
I don't think you noticed how athletic I was.
I was a relay runner.
Cowpoke, that's all for now.
I'll see you later.
Thank you very much.
We're going to play basketball.
We'll do our best
Good luck
I'll do my best.
Okay, I'm off.
Oh, what should I do?
Yay!
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Are you ready?
Oh, wow.
Oh!
I don't know... even with the starter's instructions...
You guys can't do it at all!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
What's wrong with you?
I think I'm doing pretty good for a guy like me.
I'm an athlete.I'm Mr. Athletic Performance.
Okay, that's it.
Focus.
Are you ready?
Yeah!
Wow.
That's good. That's good.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's go.
From the front.
Okay, from the front.
Let's try it.
Ah!
Oh, I'm so scared!
Wait a minute!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I understand.
Why?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
This is it.
It's good.
I can't do it.
Just say what you just said.
Ready, set, go!
Ah!
Oh!
Here we go.
Ah!
It's okay. It's okay. Calm down.
I'm coming in.
Oh, my God.
Ahhh...
I can move.
I'm moving.
Calm down.
Oh!
So close. So close.
It's okay. It's okay.
Let's do it again.
Ready?
I'm in, I'm in!
Ah!
I got it.
Go, go, go, go!
And then...
Two more!
A little more.
One more.
One more time.
Oh...
One more...
Ahhh...
I did my best
This is...
That was Louie five times.
It was six.
Six.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is my team.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ready?
Let's move on.
The secret path for you
More stones for you
Celebrate your birthday
Birthdays, like this one
See what someone is ready for one
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
A-ha-ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
It's so bright
I can't tell the distance!
Are you okay?
Please help me, I can't stand up.
I'm not standing up.Ready.
Yay!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
LOL!
Okay, I'll explain the rules.
Rock, paper, scissors!
How about it?
The red team will play first.
Here we go!
All right, let's start!
Pee!
Aaaaah!
Ahh!
I'm glad you didn't mind the plan.
I'm too friendly on the way out.
I'm going to make my way across the street
I can't stand it!
Published with a mouthful
cat is the author
cat metallic
N mit
nostalgic
cat af
why
Standing position is Homuro air
shouting
Thank you for watching!
Start
One of us didn't get in.
We've been hit by two!
Help! Help!
Help!
We're down to three.
Help! Help!
Let's get started.
It's over!
The winner of the Hanjyu at the inn is you all!
Good!
Boom!